What's happening in Sudan and how you can help.
Sudan is currently experiencing a civil war.
The fighting began in April and since then over 9,000 people have lost their life.
The conflict comes from weeks of tension between the Rapid Support Forces and the Sudanese Armed Forces
over security force reform during negotiations for a new transitional government.
Ironically, the last transitional government was overthrown by the Rapid Support Forces
and the Sudanese Armed Forces jointly in October 2021.
Innocent civilians in Sudan are being killed and displaced.
As the conflict continues to rage, thousands of lives are being needlessly lost.
Not to mention the devastating impact the war is having on women and children.
Recently released reports detailed sexual violence against women and girls.
Targeted attacks on civilian buildings such as hospitals and churches.
Many businesses have been subject to extensive eating.
In the space of six months, more than 3.3 million people have been displaced.
This includes 2.6 million people being displaced inside Sudan
and more than 738,000 people having to flee to neighbouring countries.
Saving this post makes the algorithm see it as valuable and in turn shown to more people.
The more people that sees it, the better.